[
  {
    "question": "What color are Dorthy's Slippers in The Wizard of Oz?",
    "choice1": "Ruby",
    "choice2": "Pink",
    "choice3": "Blue",
    "choice4": "Green",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Spongebob's work?",
    "choice1": "Oyster Outlet",
    "choice2": "Rocking Swordfish",
    "choice3": "Chum Bucket",
    "choice4": "Krusty Krab",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "How many donuts is in a bakers dozen?",
    "choice1": "Fourteen",
    "choice2": "Twelve",
    "choice3": "Thirteen",
    "choice4": "Eleven",
    "answer": 3
  }
    {
    "question": "What planet has the moon Titan?",
    "choice1": "Neptune",
    "choice2": "Saturn",
    "choice3": "Jupiter",
    "choice4": "Venus",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the main actor in Ferris Bueller's Day Off?",
    "choice1": "Charlie Sheen",
    "choice2": "Matthew Broderick",
    "choice3": "Keanu Reeves",
    "choice4": "Bill Murray",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What country has the city Astana?",
    "choice1": "Russia",
    "choice2": "Nepal",
    "choice3": "Dominican Republic",
    "choice4": "Khazakstan",
    "answer": 4
  }
    {
    "question": "What year did the National Atlantic Treaty Organization(NATO) form?",
    "choice1": "1939",
    "choice2": "1949",
    "choice3": "1929",
    "choice4": "1944",
    "answer": 2
  }
    {
    "question": "What year did the movie '2 Fast 2 Furious' come out?",
    "choice1": "2003",
    "choice2": "2002",
    "choice3": "2004",
    "choice4": "2001",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was John Glen?",
    "choice1": "Maker of of the Shake Weight",
    "choice2": "Founder of Scholastic",
    "choice3": "First man to orbit the Moon",
    "choice4": "Former Vice President",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What country has more people?",
    "choice1": "Indonesia",
    "choice2": "Japan",
    "choice3": "Russia",
    "choice4": "Germany",
    "answer": 1
  }
  
]
